Asya: Hello Everyone Friends, Welcome to Our Channel
Today we'll play Kung-fu-- Watermelon--
Seyit: We're going to make a rascal for the watermelon
We're going to make watermelon kerata (slowed down)
But-- (hitting the watermelon) I see the watermelon is a hit
Dividing
Asya: Yes (Seyit breaks the watermelon)
Seyit: The director (Asya's mother) was going to beat us up for making a mess, but we intervened.
(Asya hits watermelon)
Asya: ufff that hurt so much
Seyit: (grinning) BANE
(BANE music playing in the background) Seyit shows the watermelons he broke
(BANE music playing in the background) Seyit: Come on
(BANE music playing in the background) Seyit continues to show the watermelons he broke
[Black screen]
Behind the Scenes: Seyit calls out to Esma: Dump Esma Dump
(Video Ended, Don't Forget To Subscribe, Like For More) Subtitle: Hayat Drubunu 2024, all rights reserved.